(Sheldon:)Yep, you're mad.
(Howard:)Okay, let me see the damage.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Hang on.
(Howard:)Well, I think you
broke the dowels.
(Howard:)You're not gonna
have time to glue it
(Howard:)back on--
you'll have to nail it.
(Raj:)With what?
(Howard:)Does she have any
pillows or wine glasses?
(Howard:)She does.
(Howard:)Great.
(Howard:)Neither of those.
Try a hammer!
(Raj:)Did that feel good?
(Raj:)You feel like a big man now?
(Sheldon:)I was going to make you
red zinger,
(Sheldon:)but since Mars
is the red planet,
(Sheldon:)I went with peppermint.
(Amy:)Why do you even want to do this?
(Sheldon:)Actually...
(Sheldon:)as part of the application,
(Sheldon:)I was required
to make a short video
(Sheldon:)answering that very question.